Guide to the Seven Woods Press Records 1970-1986
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Oversize
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Proof, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Research, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Goldbarth, Albert, Opticks, Publicity, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Mayes, Frances, After Such Pleasures, Proof, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Cover, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Molesworth, Charles, Words to That Effect, Proof, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Cultural Post 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Cultural Post 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Cultural Post 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, Cultural Post 1980 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Schaeffer, Susan, The Witch and the Weather Report, Cover, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Advertising, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - American Library Association 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Awards and Press, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Book Affair, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Book Exhibits, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Book Exhibits, New York Fair, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Doreski, William, The Testament of Israel Potter, Cover, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dustbooks, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - New York City Poetry Calendar, 1980-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Oles, Carol, Coming into the United Society of Believers, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Other Publishing Companies, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Poetry Readings, 1974-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Publishing Services, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Wright, Jay, Soothsayers and Omens, Proof, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Restricted
  Series IV, Restricted, includes financial material that is restricted until 2033.
  - Business Loan, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Financial, Checks, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Financial, Checks, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Financial, Checks, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Financial, Checks, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Financial, Checks, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Financial, Checks, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Financial, Checks, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Financial, Checks, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Financial, Checks, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Financial, Checks, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Financial, Checks, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Financial, Checks, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Financial, Deposits, 1972-1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Financial, Special Claims and Bankruptcy, 1973-1981 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Financial, Statements, 1973-1983 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Financial, Statements, 1976-1983 (Box 28, Folder 2)